摇动你的尾巴!
We've just got the day to get ready
我们只有一天的时间可以准备
And there's only so much time to lose
可没多少能浪费的时间
Because tonight  yeah  we're here to party
因为今晚 我们要在这儿狂欢
So let's think of something fun to do
让我们想想有些什么好玩的吧
We don't know we don't know what's gonna happen
我们不知道会发生什么
We just know we just know it's gonna feel right
我们只知道这会感觉很好
All our friends are here
我们所有的朋友都在这儿
And it's time to ignite the lights
是时候点燃所有的灯啦
Shake your tail 'cause we're here to have a party tonight
摇摇你的尾巴吧 因为我们今晚将在这里彻夜狂欢
Shake your tail  shake your tail
欢快地摇摇你的尾巴吧
Shake your tail 'cause we're here to have a party tonight
摇摇你的尾巴吧 因为我们今晚将在这里彻夜狂欢
Shake your tail  shake your tail
欢快地摇摇你的尾巴吧
So what you didn't get it right the first time
所以当你第一次没有做好时
Laugh it off  no one said it is a crime
那就一笑而过吧 没人说那是一种罪行
Do your thing you know you're an original
做你自己的事儿 你会知道你就是原创者
Your ideas are so funny that they're criminal
你的想法实在太有趣了 竟然想到他们有罪
Ohhh ahh
We've just got the day
我们只有一天的时间
to get ready
可以准备
And there's only so much time to lose
可没多少能浪费的时间
Because tonight  yeah  we're here to party
因为今晚 我们要在这儿狂欢
So let's think of something fun to do
让我们想想有些什么好玩的吧
We don't know we don't know what's gonna happen
我们不知道会发生什么
We just know we just know it's gonna feel right
我们只知道这会感觉很好
All our friends are here
我们所有的朋友都在这
And it's time to ignite the lights
是时候点燃所有的灯啦
Shake your tail 'cause we're here to have a party tonight
摇摇你的尾巴吧 因为我们今晚将在这里彻夜狂欢
Shake your tail shake your tail
欢快地摇摇你的尾巴
Shake your tail 'cause we're here to have a party tonight
摇摇你的尾巴吧 因为我们今晚将在这里彻夜狂欢
Shake your tail shake your tail
欢快地摇摇你的尾巴吧
Shake your tail 'cause we're here to have a party tonight
摇摇你的尾巴吧 因为我们今晚将在这里彻夜狂欢
Shake your tail shake your tail
欢快地摇摇你的尾巴吧
Shake your tail 'cause we're here to have a party tonight
摇摇你的尾巴吧 因为我们今晚将在这里彻夜狂欢
Shake your tail shake your tail
欢快地摇摇你的尾巴吧
Shake your tail 'cause we're here to have a party tonight
摇摇你的尾巴吧 因为我们今晚将在这里彻夜狂欢